A.D.
M.
Due to its declining birthrate of the human popula- tion,
Akibat dari turunnya tingkat kelahiran populasi manusia,
this country has turned into a nation of cats.
negara ini menjadi negeri para kucing.
Cat Country Japan.
Negara Kucing Jepang
A School Cats Can Attend
Sekolah yang Kucing Bisa Masuk
Sora… Sora! Wake up!
Sora… Sora! Bangun!
What is it, Mugishima?
Ada apa, Mugishima?
We're here.
Kita sudah sampai loh.
So this is a school where us, cats, can go to?
Jadi ini sekolah yang kucing bisa masuk, ya?
That's right.
Benar.
Even cats want to go to school too, huh?
Kucing pun juga ada yang ingin bersekolah, ya?
You didn't know?
Kamu enggak tahu?
A school is a place you can sleep really well.
Sekolah itu tempat di mana kamu bisa tidur nyenyak, loh.
Books for Cat
Buku Khusus Kucing
Human and Cats
Manusia & Kucing
There's a limit to what we can experience in life.
Hal yang bisa kami alami dalam hidup itu terbatas.
That might be why we try to gain experience through books.
Mungkin karena itulah kami mencoba menambah pengalaman lewat buku.
Sign when you'll taken to the vet:
Tanda-tanda akan dibawa ke dokter hewan:
a pet carrier…
kandang jinjing…
I'm learning things I'd rather not know.
Aku jadi dapat pengalaman yang tidak perlu.
Books for Human
Buku Khusus Manusia
Hmm, hmm.
Hmm, hmm.
Let's see what your book is about, Mugishima—
Coba kita lihat bukumu tentang apa, Mugishima—
Using a laundry net…
Menggunakan jaring cucian…
…to the vet.
…untuk dibawa ke dokter hewan.
Huh??????????????
Ehhh??????????????
Uhm, how about we look up for a regular book instead?
Anu, gimana kalau kita cari buku yang biasa aja?
Oh, good point. Let's go put it back.
Oh, iya juga. Yuk kita balikkan bukunya.
Now, let's see… I think I got it from around here…
Coba kuingat... Kayaknya aku mengambilnya di sekitar sini...
…and it was taken by the cat.
…tempatnya.
You can just leave it to me, I'll put it back on the shelf.
Kamu bisa taruh bukunya di situ, nanti saya bereskan.
Oh, alright.
Ah, baik.
Cats can get into any tight space, you know.
Namanya juga kucing, suka masuk ke celah sempit di mana pun ya.
Ooh.
Ooh.
A book's empty spot… I'll remember that.
Celah bekas buku, ya… Patut dicatat, nih.
Ooh, ooh.
Ooh, ooh.
He's learned yet another useless thing.
Dia belajar yang tidak penting lagi.
TL TM TS MX-QC A segment of this episode has been PR'd using scanslation by Sarusa. AI Transcribe was utilized
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe diutilisasikan.
: geckyzz
: geckyzz